蠃蚌
零器
Rabou.
Reiki.
弾丸込めた小銃を　僕は片手に持っている
Noragami
震えた君のいる場所へ　足を早め向かっている
チクタク　針はチクタクと
dangan kometa shoujuu wo boku wa katate ni motte iru
With a loaded rifle in one hand
チクタク　針はチクタクと
dangan kometa shoujuu wo boku wa katate ni motte iru
With a loaded rifle in one hand
チクタク　針はチクタクと
dangan kometa shoujuu wo boku wa katate ni motte iru
With a loaded rifle in one hand
チクタク　針はチクタクと
dangan kometa shoujuu wo boku wa katate ni motte iru
With a loaded rifle in one hand
チクタク　針はチクタクと
dangan kometa shoujuu wo boku wa katate ni motte iru
With a loaded rifle in one hand
焦る心を急かしただけ
dangan kometa shoujuu wo boku wa katate ni motte iru
With a loaded rifle in one hand
furueta kimi no iru basho e ashi wo hayame mukatte iru
I rush to where you stand trembling
チクタク　針はチクタクと
furueta kimi no iru basho e ashi wo hayame mukatte iru
I rush to where you stand trembling
チクタク　針はチクタクと
furueta kimi no iru basho e ashi wo hayame mukatte iru
I rush to where you stand trembling
チクタク　針はチクタクと
furueta kimi no iru basho e ashi wo hayame mukatte iru
I rush to where you stand trembling
チクタク　針はチクタクと
furueta kimi no iru basho e ashi wo hayame mukatte iru
I rush to where you stand trembling
チクタク　針はチクタクと
furueta kimi no iru basho e ashi wo hayame mukatte iru
I rush to where you stand trembling
チクタク　針はチクタクと
furueta kimi no iru basho e ashi wo hayame mukatte iru
I rush to where you stand trembling
留まる気配もなく　進んでいく
チクタク　針はチクタクと
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
chi
ku
ta
ha
ri
wa
chi
ku
ta
to
The clock is ticking
チクタク　針はチクタクと
終わりと始まりの境目
aseru kokoro wo sekashita dake
Making my heart race even faster
終わりと始まりの境目
チクタク　針はチクタクと
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
chi
ku
ta
ha
ri
wa
chi
ku
ta
to
The clock is ticking
チクタク　針はチクタクと
todomaru kehai mo naku susunde yuku
Going on and on endlessly
全て重なった
閉口して　僕は待っていた
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
chi
ku
ta
ha
ri
wa
chi
ku
ta
to
The clock is ticking
薄暗い部屋　一人きり
owari to hajimari no sakaime
In the small gap between end and beginning
薄暗い部屋　一人きり
owari to hajimari no sakaime
閉口して　僕は待っていた
chikutaku hari wa chikutaku to
chi
ku
ta
ha
ri
wa
chi
ku
ta
to
The clock is ticking
閉口して　僕は待っていた
subete kasanatta
That's where everything will happen
ドアを蹴破る　その音を
閉口して　僕は待っていた
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was waiting helplessly
閉口して　僕は待っていた
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was waiting helplessly
閉口して　僕は待っていた
薄暗い部屋　一人きり
usugurai heya hitorikiri
In this dark room all by myself
薄暗い部屋　一人きり
閉口して　僕は待っていた
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
閉口して　僕は待っていた
もう怖れることはないよ
doa wo keyaburu sono oto wo
For the sound of the door being kicked in
もう怖れることはないよ
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
弾丸込めた小銃を持って
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
弾丸込めた小銃を持って
usugurai heya hitorikiri
In this dark room all by myself
固く閉ざされたドアを蹴破った
Heikou shite boku wa matte ita
I was there waiting helplessly
吸い付いた銃口が跳ねて
mou osoreru koto wa nai yo
There's nothing to fear now
昨日の僕を貫いた
mou osoreru koto wa nai yo
おやすみ　その絶望を受け取って
dangan kometa shoujuu wo motte
With a loaded rifle in hand
おやすみ　その絶望を受け取って
dan
gan
ko
me
ta
sho
u
ju
wo
mo
明日への僕は歩き始めた
tte
kataku tozasareta doa wo keyabutta
I kick down the locked door
明日への僕は歩き始めた
ka
ta
ku
to
za
sa
re
ta
do
a
wo
ke
ya
bu
tta
また今夜　待ち合わせよう
suitsuita juukou ga hanete
The gun recoils
また今夜　待ち合わせよう
su
i
また今夜　待ち合わせよう
tsu
i
ta
ju
u
ko
ga
ha
ne
kinou no boku wo tsuranuita
As I pierce through my past self
ki
no
u
bo
ku
wo
tsu
ra
nu
i
ta
I accept the lingering despair
oyasumi sono zetsubou wo uketotte
ashita e no boku wa arukihajimeta
And start walking toward the future
mata kon'ya machiawaseyou
ma
ta
ko
n'
ya
ma
chi
a
wa
se
you
Let's meet again tonight
本字幕由诸神字幕组(kamigami.org)制作，仅供交流学习，禁止用于任何商业用途
日听:小然&云连湾  翻译:maki&迩祢  校对:木落&叶隐  时间轴:Gissa  压制:久嘉
What's going on?!
どういうことなわけ
Sounds like Yato-chan
and the others are back.
夜トちゃん達帰ってきてたんだ
When exactly did they become part of this household?
いつからあいつらうちの子になったんだ
What the heck is happening?!
よくわかんないんだけど
You should just calm down, Yato.
落ち着けって　夜ト
だって　なんなの日和のあれ
But what happened to Hiyori?!
雪音君　こちらの方…
Hey Yukine-kun,
if you don't mind me asking...
誰
Who's this guy?
え　誰って
Huh? What do you mean?
Oh, man, Hiyori! Kicking off
the new year with a joke, huh?
なになに日和　新年ジョーク？
俺だよ　俺
It's me, duh!
Itsumida-san?
俺だよ　俺…さん？
That's right! Itsumida!
YES！俺だよ　俺
Man, what nationality
was that supposed to be?
って　俺何人だよ　ほほほ
雪音君　この人　知り合い？
Is he a friend of yours, Yukine-kun?
芸人さんか何か？
Is he a comedian or something?
Huh?
あれは記憶喪失だなあ
It must be amnesia.
やっぱり！
You think so?!
なんでか夜トのことだけ綺麗に忘れちゃってるみたいだった
For some reason, she's forgotten about you and only you.
What are we gonna do?!
どうしょう
Oh, relax, will you?
ガタガタ騒ぐなよ　きっと一時的なことだろう
I'm sure it's a temporary thing.
She'll remember you soon enough.
すぐに思い出すって
No.
いやだ
Yato?
夜ト？
I will turn Hiyori back to normal.
絶対に日和を元に戻す
Chapter 11
Abandoned God
That's it! Right this way!
はいはい　こちらですよ
I actually only came to give you some more of my old books.
私　参考書を渡しに来ただけなんだけど
ちょっと付き合ってあげてよ
Just play along for a bit.
左手に見えますのが
If you look to your left,
you'll see the legendary street
あの　有名な
夜ト神と少女が上様を助けた伝説の道でございます
where the famous god named Yato
and a girl rescued Milord!
えっ
Huh?!
A lord used to pass through here?!
上様が通ったんですか
ここって　そんなに歴史ある道だったんですね
I had no idea this was
such a historical location!
I don't think she remembers.
思い出さないみたいだな
どちらの上様なんですか　夜トさん
Which lord was it, Yato-san?
"-san"?!
さん付け
It's "Yato"! You used to call me
just "Yato," without any honorific!
夜トって
呼び捨てにしてたじゃん　前は夜トって
でも　いきなり呼び捨ては失礼ですし
But it would be rude to call you that since we just met.
Look, Hiyori!
日和　見ろ
ちょっと　また俺のノートに
Wha... Not my notebook again!
MILORD
This is Milord! This!
これが上様　これが
MILORD
Oh!
夜トさん　絵がお上手ですね
You're really good at drawing, Yato-san!
食いついて欲しいのはそこじゃないです日和さん
That isn't what I'm trying
to show you, Hiyori-san!
Oh, that's right!
Milord was the cat's name!
あ　そっか　上様って猫の名前でしたね
思い出したか
It's coming back to you?
Do you remember who I am, too?!
じゃ　俺のことも
えっと
Let me see...
A manga artist?
漫画家さん
私　もう行かなきゃ
I need to get going now.
雪音君　勉強はまた今度でいい
Could we have your lesson
another time, Yukine-kun?
次までの宿題は中に入ってるから
All your homework until then is in here.
Yeah, sure.
あっ　うん
See you later!
じゃ
Hiyori!
日和
Hiyori...
日和　本当に忘れちまったのか
Have you really forgotten me?
You really can't remember me?
俺のこと　思い出さないのか
In that case...
じゃ
Get in bed with me.
一緒に布団に入ってくれ
It might remind you of when
we met at the hospital—
そうすれば　俺と病院で会ったことを思い出すかも
Pervert!
変態！
夜トちゃんたち　夜ごはんは後でいいって
Yato-chan and Yukki said
they'd have dinner later.
So they're still gonna eat here, huh?
食べることは食べるのね
A memory picture show?
思い出の紙芝居って？
そんなんで記憶が戻るのかね
Will that really bring back her memory?
いや　行ける
It will! You saw how she
reacted to my drawing!
俺の絵を見た時あの反応
日和の中の何かを呼び起こしたに違いない
It definitely sparked something
inside Hiyori's mind!
Now quit slacking off and help me!
お前もぼさっとしないで手伝え！
No way. This is so childish.
やだよ　そんなガキみたいなこと
なんで
I wonder...
なんであの人　あんなに必死なんだろう
I wonder why that guy seemed so desperate.
All right!
よし　これで完璧な紙芝居が出来る
Now I can make the
perfect picture show!
It won't be long now!
あと一息だしな
I can't believe you spent all your 5-yen coins to buy art supplies.
まさか画材一式に五円玉貯金全部叩くとは
待ってろよ　日和！
Just you wait, Hiyori!
Still, why can't Hiyori remember?
でも本当　なんでこんなことになったんだろう
Yato?
夜ト
What's wrong?
なんだ
I should've known you
were behind this, Nora.
やっぱりお前が何かしたんだな　野良
I stole her memories of you.
もらっちゃった　夜トに関する記憶をね
とても簡単だったわ
It was very easy, actually.
私たちみたいな彼岸のものとの思い出なんて
She has no need for memories of Far Shore denizens like us.
いらないものね
People are quick to forget you, anyway.
人はすぐにあなたのことを忘れる
そうでしょう
Wouldn't you agree?
あなたがどんなに願いを叶えても
In spite of how much
you grant humans' wishes,
人の思いは気まぐれで移ろい易い
their feelings will always
be fickle and erratic.
Poor Yato. You've been hurt so many times.
今まで何度も何度も泣かされて 可哀想な夜ト
本当のあなたを思い出して
Remember your true self.
Yato!
夜ト
Don't listen to her!
あいつの言うことに耳を貸しちゃダメだ
雪音
Yukine...
野良　今度は何企んでる
Nora, what are you plotting this time?!
夜トが私たちのところに来ればいいなって思って
I was just hoping that you might visit us.
Furu
Reiki.
零器
Y-You...
お　お前
蠃蚌
Rabou!
You're alive?
生きてたのか
It's been a while, Yato.
久しいな　夜ト神
Wh-Who is he?
誰
What's with that sun visor you're wearing?
なんだ　そのサンバイザー
参るぞ
Have at you.
Come, Sekki!
こい　雪器
ちょっ　夜ト　いいのかよ！
Whoa! Are you trying to kill him, Yato?!
If I hold back at all against this guy...
こいつは本気で行かねぇと　こっちがやられちまう
he'll kill me!
He's as fast as ever!
相変わらず早い
Yato...
夜ト神
What has happened to you?
どうしたんだ
This is not the extent of your power.
お前の力はこんなものではない
思い出せ
Remember...
Remember.
思い出せ
Remember. Remember.
Remember. Remember. Remember.
思い出せ 思い出せ 思い出せ
Remember. Remember!
思い出せ 思い出せ
Yato!
夜ト
You okay, Yato? Yato?!
夜ト大丈夫かよ
夜ト
As for the next report...
次の報告ですが
What is this?
これは
What's happening?!
何ごとだ
Y-Yato!
夜…夜ト
Yukine!
雪音
You were right.
やはり　これはわれの知っている夜ト神ではないぞ
This isn't the Yato I knew, Furuhime.
零姫
So now you understand?
でも　わかったでしょう
Listen, Yato.
ね　夜ト
If you can beat Rabou,
I'll give Iki Hiyori her memory back.
夜トが蠃蚌に勝ったら
あの子　壱岐日和の記憶を返してあげる
約束よ
I promise.
Noragami
No
ra
では　この異常な時化の発生は
Then, concerning this unusual storm...
No
ra
ga
No
ra
ga
No
ra
ga
No
ra
ga
No
ra
ga
mi
No
ra
ga
mi
No
ra
ga
mi
No
ra
ga
mi
ra
ga
mi
No
ra
ga
mi
ra
ga
mi
ra
ga
mi
ra
ga
mi
Nope.
ああ　うちのかみさんは関係ねえ
mi
ga
ra
No
My lady has nothing to do with it.
I came to ask if a Vent
had opened unexpectedly.
予期せぬ風穴でも開いたかと来てみたが
I never would have thought
it had to do with Yato.
まさか夜トが関係していたとは
俺たち　その蠃蚌ってやつに全然敵わなくて
We were no match for
that Rabou guy at all.
Rabou?
蠃蚌
Never heard of him.
きかねえ名前だな
Rabou is a god of calamity.
まがつかみ　蠃蚌
No one really talks about him these days,
今ではその名を聞くこともないが
but he used to be really
well known a long time ago.
かつては知られた名だったらしい
ご存知なんですか
You know him?
蠃蚌はもともと人間でね
Rabou was originally human, you see.
As I recall, in life he served as a Herald.
確か生前は御先をやっていたはずだよ
Herald?
御先
間者として敵陣に忍び込む
A spy who sneaks into enemy territory to conduct dirty work.
いわば汚れ仕事だね
Once a Herald finishes their job,
御先は仕事が終わると
their master kills them to ensure silence.
口封じのため　主に殺される
That's awful!
そんな
They say that after his death,
people who feared being cursed
彼は死後
祟りを恐れた人々に奉られ
deified him and made him
a god of calamity.
生まれたまがつかみだと聞いている
A god of calamity?
あの　まがつかみって
People don't always wish for good things.
人の願いはいいものばかりではない
There are evil wishes, too.
悪い願いもある
Evil wishes?
悪い願い
Wanting to eliminate someone
you hate, for example.
憎い相手を消して欲しいとかだよ
A god of calamity is one that answers such wicked wishes.
そんな邪な願いに応えるのが
まがつかみだ
In particular, Rabou granted
people's wishes through killing.
中でも　蠃蚌は斬ることで人々の願いを叶えていた
They say he has killed people, Phantoms...
それこそ望まれれば
人もあやかしも
and even other gods, if requested.
神でさえも斬った　とか
Wh-What does someone
like that want with Hiyori?
そ　そんなやつがなんで日和を
Is he an old pal of Yato's?
夜トの昔の仲間か
I have heard rumors...
噂で聞いたことがある
that a god of calamity
once fought alongside Yato.
夜トとともに戦ったまがつかみがいたと
Rabou hasn't changed at all.
蠃蚌は昔のままだった
He's still powerful.
あいつは強い
If I'm not careful,
he could end up killing Yukine.
下手すりゃ　雪音がやられちまう
But shouldn't it be difficult for a god of calamity like him to continue existing?
しかし
あのようなまがつかみが存在し続けるのは難しいはず
ちょ　ちょっと待ってくれよ
H-Hold on a minute!
Yato and Rabou were partners?
夜トと蠃蚌が仲間って
Does that mean Yato's
a god of calamity, too?!
まさか　夜トもまがつかみだってこと
I-I never knew—
そんなの知らない
Hiyorin knows.
ひよりんは知ってるよ
I was the one who told her.
前に私が教えたの
It didn't seem to bother her one bit, though.
けど　んなことおくびにも出さなかったなあ
Hiyori-chan's one tough girl, all right.
ひよりちゃん　ありゃ強い女だ
Yato-chan's different now.
夜トちゃん　変わったもん
That's why she stuck with him.
だから一緒にいてくれたんだよ
Hiyorin must really love you and Yato-chan!
ひよりんは夜トちゃんとゆっきのことが大好きなんだね
I...
俺　ひよりの記憶を取り戻したい
want to bring Hiyori's memory back!
At this rate, Hiyori will never remember me.
このままひよりは俺を忘れて
それでいいんじゃないかな
Perhaps it's for the best.
As I said before,
you should cut your ties with her.
言ったでしょ
縁を斬ればって
Your connection gets her
too involved in our world.
あの子は君を介して　こちらに焦点を合わせすぎている
Maintaining that connection would keep her from living on her own.
自分の世界を生きられなくなるよ
今のまま夜ト君を忘れれば
If she forgets about you, she'll likely stop changing into a half-Phantom.
半妖化することもなくなるだろう
That will give her happiness.
それがあの子の幸せだよ
It appears he's made up his mind.
心を決めたようじゃな
Yato-san...
夜トさん
Yato!
夜ト
Where have you been?
何してたんだよ
I've been thinking
about Hiyori's memory—
俺さ　考えたんだけど
ひよりの記憶
Forget it.
もういい
ひよりのことはもういいんだ
Just forget about Hiyori.
Huh?!
Hey, Yato! Yato!
おい夜ト　夜ト
時が惜しい
There is no time to waste.
Even now while I wait,
time endlessly slips through my fingers.
こうして待つ間も
われの時は刻々とこぼれ落ちてゆく
Don't worry.
大丈夫よ
Yato will return.
きっと夜トは戻ってくるわ
I'm sure of it.
きっとね
And then...
でね
Yukki! Did you see Yato-chan?
ゆっき　夜トちゃんには会えた
Man...
ったく
What's Yato's deal?!
He's not making any sense!
なんだよ　夜トのやつ
意味わかんねえ
Why is he suddenly...
なんで急に
The Tale of Hiyori
and the Yato God
Looks like I really did know him.
私　やっぱり前はあの人のこと　知ってたんだ
If only I could remember...
思い出してあげられたらいいなぁ
Yukine-kun?
雪音くん
Hiyori!
ひより
Sorry to keep you waiting!
わるい　待たせた
Oh, don't worry.
どうしたの
So, what's up?
Here.
これ
Wow! A picture play!
紙芝居
Did you make it?
作ったの
Yeah.
Will you watch it?
見てくれる
Okay.
じゃ　万年ジャージーの神様 夜ト神と日和の物語
This is the story of Yato—
the sweats-wearing god—and Hiyori.
Let the story begin!
始まり始まり
Yukine is with Hiyori again?
雪音のやつ
またひよりといるのか
And so the gifted Regalia drew
a Borderline on his very first try!
天才神器である彼は　一発で境界線を引けたのです
Yes, yes! You're amazing, Yukine-kun!
そうそう　すごいよね　雪音くん
Even Yato was surprised when I did it!
あの時は夜トも驚いてたよな
Oh... He was?
そうなの
Um, and then...
えっと　それで
Yato.
夜ト
Know what this is?
これな～んだ
そして禊は成功して
The ablution was a success,
and thanks to Yato and Hiyori...
夜トとひよりのおかげで
Thanks to Yato and Hiyori
being there for me,
夜トとひよりがいてくれたから
I managed to become normal again.
俺は戻ってこれました
And that's how...
こうして
Yato
Me
Hiyori
A-And that's how Hiyori, Yato, and I...
こ こうして
俺とひよりと夜トは仲良くなりました
all became good friends.
I'm sorry. I still can't remember Yato-san.
ごめんね
やっぱり夜トさんのことは思い出せない
But it sounds like we're good friends.
でも　私たちは仲良しなんだね
Hiyori
Me
Yato
Yeah... Yeah!
Say, Yukine-kun.
ねぇ　雪音くん
Could I have that notebook?
そのノート　私にちょうだい
Huh?! Oh, but...
あ いや　でも
なんか　それがあれば
I feel like it might somehow help me remember what I've forgotten.
忘れちゃってることも思い出せそうな気がする
In that case...
だったら
It's really waning now.
随分欠けたね
Tell me, Yato.
ねぇ　夜ト
Where do you suppose the
waning part of the moon falls?
欠けた月はどこに落ちると思う
Falls?
落ちる
Hiyori?
ひより
Hiyo—
ひよ
Is this yours?
これ　君の？
Yukine...
雪音
What have you done, Nora?!
何した　野良
Iki Hiyori's memory is
waning bit by bit, falling away.
壱岐ひよりの記憶はね
少しずつ欠け落ちていくんだよ
早く来ないと
If you don't pay us a visit soon...
あの子　空っぽの器になっちゃうね
there'll be nothing left.
Hiyori's forgotten about me too.
ひより
俺のことも忘れちゃった
She's forgotten!
忘れちゃったよ
Yukine...
雪音
We're going to go
bring her memory back.
ひよりの記憶を取り戻しに行く
だが
But a fight against them
could end up destroying you.
あいつらと戦えば　お前を壊しちまうかもしれない
Yato...
夜ト
And I might just be giving them exactly what they want.
俺自身　あいつらの思惑にハマっちまうことも
"Believe in yourself!"
自分を信じろ
Those were your own words.
そう言ったのは夜トだろう
This... is me?
これ　私
A tail?
尻尾
Hiyori! It's time!
ひより　時間よ
Hiyori!
ひより
Um...
あの
I'm sorry for losing my cool back there.
ごめん
色々忘れて　不安なのはひよりのほうなのに
You're probably the one most
troubled by forgetting all this.
俺　自分のことばっかでテンパっちゃって
なんか　とんでもないことにひよりを巻き込んで
We've dragged you
into something terrible.
Although, technically,
his twisted past is entirely to blame.
つうか　全部こいつの面倒くさい過去のせいだけど
But he is my master,
でも　こんなでも俺の主だし
and what's my master's is also mine, so...
主のことは俺のことでもあるわけだし
Say something too, Yato!
夜トもなんか言えよ
We will bring your memory back.
お前の記憶は必ず取り戻す
So just rest easy and wait, Hiyori.
だから安心して待ってろ　ひより
Hiyori? What's wrong?!
ひより　どうしたの
I'm not sure.
わかりません
I'm not really sure.
わからないけど
Stop crying.
もう泣くな
Let's go.
行くぞ
Whatever happens I will surely call out your name
ki
mi
no
na
ma
e
na
ni
ga
a
tte
mo
ka
na
ra
zu
yo
bu
ka
ra
君の名前 何があっても
必ず呼ぶから
Your heart is all jagged
ki
mi
wa
gi
za
ha
a
to
no
mo
chi
nu
shi
君はぎざぎざハートの持ち主
So you hurt anything you touch
fu
re
ru
mo
no
wa
na
n
de
mo
ki
zu
tsu
ke
ru
触れるものは何でも傷つけ
Those eyes that frown at everything
se
ka
i
no
su
be
te
wo
ni
ra
mi
tsu
ke
te
世界のすべてを睨み付けて
その目は言うんだ
They are saying "I'm here! See me!"
so
no
me
wa
i
un
da
bo
ku
wa
ko
ni
iru
「僕はここにいる」
Someone was laughing at you
da
re
ka
ga
wa
ra
tte
ta
誰かが笑ってた
だから引いたんだ その境界線
So you put that barrier around you
da
ka
ra
hi
i
tan
da
so
no
kyo
u
ka
i
sen
But I'll reach in there with my hand
so
re
na
ra
wa
ta
shi
ga
so
no
te
wo
hi
ku
それなら
私はその手を引く
さぁ
And bring you out
tsu
re
te
ku
ka
ra
連れてくから
If you don't have words, just grasp my hand
i
e
na
i
ra
ko
no
te
wo
tsu
yo
ku
ni
gi
tte
言えないなら
この手を強く握って
And don't let go
ha
na
sa
i
de
離さないで
君はもう一人じゃないんだって
I want you to know that you
ki
mi
wa
mo
u
hi
to
ri
ja
na
i
n
da
tte
知ってほしいんだよ
Are not alone any more
shi
tte
ho
shi
in
da
yo
Ding-ding! It's time for a Regalia midterm test!
じゃんじゃんじゃん　ここで神器中間テスト
List ten good things about your master!
主のいいところを十個述べよ
Ten?!
十個？
どうした　雪音
What's the matter, Yukine?
Five would be okay, I suppose.
五個でもいいぞ
Five...
五個
On the next Noragami:
"A Scrap of a Memory."
次回 ノラガミ　一片の記憶
Fine! Just three, then!
ベストスリーでも許す
Sorry, can't think of any.
ダメだごめん
A Scrap of a Memory
Next Episode
夜ト　俺まじで浮かない
Whoa, whoa! Does nothing come to mind?!
いやいやいや　そんなにない